[Music]
This information is our opinion only and
not financial advice. Please do your own research before making any decisions.
We are not liable for any profits or losses.
ICAI Lord General
Insurance Company has released its latest
shareholding report, which
covers the quarters and first half of the financial year ending June 30, 2024.
This report provides detailed information on the company's shares held by
promoters, promoter
groups, foreign investors, public
investors, and government entities.
Promoter shareholding has
increased from 51.27% in March 2024 to 51.8% in June 2024.
This
increase clearly indicates that promoters'
control over the company has strengthened. The
percentage of public health shares held has declined from
9.56% in March 2024 to 6.97% in June 2024.
This decline clearly indicates that the
public's stake in the company has declined during this time period.
increased its shareholding from 16.11 in March 2024 to 17.2 in June 2024. This indicates
that domestic institutions have
increased their interest in the company by 1.18.
FII (Foreign Institutional
Investors) have increased their shareholding by 23.06.19
in March 2024.
Let us
look at the investor statistics that can
cause fluctuations in shareholding pattern.
III Bank Limited has shown a
significant improvement in stakeholding this quarter, with a
significant increase of 0.54. Bhartiya
Enterprises Limited held
2 shares in the previous quarter but has
exited the company in the current quarter.
Mutual
Fund Slash saw an increase in stakeholding in the latest quarter, with an
update of 1.59.
UTI Mutual Fund
through various schemes
saw an increase in stakeholding in the latest quarter, with an update of 0.01.
Nippon Life
Mutual Fund through various schemes
saw an increase in stake holding, which
saw an uptake of 0.09% ICCR
Prudential Mutual Fund through various
schemes has decreased its stake to
2.94% from 3.58% in the previous quarter.
This shows a stake difference of -0.64% in the corresponding quarters
SBI Mutual
Fund through various schemes has
decreased its stake to 4.16% from 4.39% in the previous quarter.
This shows a
stake difference of -0.23% in the corresponding quarters
Alternate
Investment Funds saw an increase in stake holding in the latest quarter,
which saw an uptake of 0.01%
Insurance Companies have
decreased their stake to 1.13% from 1.49% in the previous quarter.
This shows a
stake difference of -0.36% in the corresponding quarters
Provident Funds and Pension Funds have decreased
their stake to 1.13% from 0.57% in the previous quarter.  has
decreased to 0.52
This
shows a difference of -0.05 stakes
across the consecutive quarters The mutual funds through various schemes entered the
company with 1.33 shares in the current quarter
whereas in the previous quarter
they held % shares The funds through various
funds used to own 1 shares in the previous quarter
but in the current
quarter they have exited the company
A notable increase
of 0.82 in their stake holding was
seen in the previous quarter
A notable increase of 0.04 in
their stake holding was seen
in the previous quarter
A notable increase of 0.07 in their
stake holding was
seen in the previous quarter
Government  of Singapore used to
own shares at Rs. 1 in the previous quarter but
in the current quarter he has exited the company
but this was the current share
holding pattern of the company. Thanks for watching.
Subscribe to the channel for stock latest news updates and like and share the video.